CONTACT



+249127897927



hind.hisham.alsadig@gmail.com



Sudan-Gadarif

SKILLS

Microsoft Office

GIMP 2D, Blender 3D Graphic progames

HTML, JS, CSS Web langauge

Libraries jQuery,Three JS

Frameworks Bootstrap, React

LANGUAGES

Arabic

English

HOBBIES

reading

writing

drawing

HIND HISHAM ALSADIG

Front-End Developer

OBJECTIVE

helping companies create and maintain a better code base for reusability, Capable of continuous learning from the senior developers while still nurturing junior developers.

Experience in driving projects forward as the development team leader, facilitating projects from concept to launch.

Passionate about learning and development with a desire to apply skills problems and continue to find ways to maximize user efficiency.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science:

Computer Science - 2014 Gadarif University.

EXPERIENCE

front-end trainer 2023-present

SSTC

computer teacher 2020-present

English school of Almerghani school

computer teacher 2013-2014

Bona Computer Center

References

Ahmed Shoghey +249919028594

SSTC Manager and owner

Ismail Ibrahim +249119182609

Almerghani school manager